[
  {
    "question": "根据表格中提供的信息，在横线上回答问题",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "《A picnic》 Date: Friday, June 9th; Time:11 o'clock in the morning",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Place: Shanghai Zoo; Participants: Students of Grade 5;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Food for lunch:Bring the food you like; Activities: Play ball games",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "1.Is it Friday?",
    "answers": ["Yes, it is."]
  },
  {
    "question": "2.Is the picnic in the afternoon?",
    "answers": ["No, it isn't.", "No, it is not."]
  },
  {
    "question": "3.Where are the students going?",
    "answers": ["They are going to Shanghai Zoo."]
  },
  {
    "question": "4.Can they eat and play there?",
    "answers": ["Yes, they can."]
  },
  {
    "question": "5.Who can have a picnic on that day?",
    "answers": ["Students of Grade 5."]
  },
  {
    "question": "写出动词的现在分词形式",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "work",
    "answers": ["working"]
  },
  {
    "question": "sit",
    "answers": ["sitting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "drop",
    "answers": ["dropping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "判断划线部分发音，用T/F表示",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "(E)leven tw(e)lve",
    "answers": ["F", "f"]
  },
  {
    "question": "dr(aw) f(our)teen",
    "answers": ["T", "t"]
  },
  {
    "question": "阅读信息，填写英语单词，完成短文（字数不限）",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Name: Eddie; Age: Eleven;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Class: Class Four, Grade Four;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Student number: 22; Hobby: reading and skating;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Address: No.12, Garden Road; Phone number: 5669432;",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, I'm Eddie. I am a pupil from (   ).",
    "answers": ["Class Four, Grade Four"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the class, my number is (   ).",
    "answers": ["22"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I love (   ) very much. I live at No.12, on Garden Road.",
    "answers": ["reading and skating"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you want to see me, please dial 5669432. Please remember my (   ). Maybe we can be friends.",
    "answers": ["Phone Number", "Phone number", "phone number"]
  }
]
